Captioning Provided By:
MTV Networks
字幕提供者：
MTV网络
Are ya ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
Kids: Aye, aye, Captain.
孩子们：是的，是的，队长。
I can't  hear  you.
我听不到你说话。
Kids:
Aye, aye, Captain.
孩子们：
是的，是的，船长。
♪ Ohh... ♪
♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
队长：♪ 吸水性的，黄色的
他是多孔的 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ If nautical nonsense
be somethin' you wish ♪
船长：♪ 如果是航海方面的废话
成为你所希望的那样 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
船长：♪ 然后降落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Ready? ♪
队长：♪ 准备好了吗？ ♪
All: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
全部： ♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ SpongeBob
SquarePants ♪
队长：♪ 海绵宝宝
方裤♪
Plankton: Ha, ha.
浮游生物：哈哈哈。
Hold it right there, Plankton.
坚持住，浮游生物。
Krabs.
螃蟹。
I'll take that.
我会接受的。
How did you know it was me?
你怎么知道是我？
Next time, wear a disguise
without your initial on it.
下次请乔装打扮
上面没有您名字的首字母缩写。
Hmm... Perhaps a pepper shaker
was a bit obvious.
嗯...也许是胡椒瓶
有点明显了。
You think?
您认为？
SpongeBob?
海绵宝宝？
Man: Three, two, one, launch.
男：三、二、一，发射。
Plankton: Never.
浮游生物：从来没有。
Never  .
绝不  。
I'll never get Krabs's formula.
我永远不会得到蟹老板的配方。
Mr. Krabs is too powerful.
蟹老板太厉害了。
If only there were a way
to render him helpless.
要是有办法就好了
让他无助。
Woman: Aw, look at you.
女：噢，看看你。
You're so small,
tiny and helpless.
你还那么小，
渺小而无助。
Hey, I resent that... Huh?
嘿，我很反感……嗯？
Why, you're so
tiny and helpless
为何你如此
渺小而无助
I could take your formula
whenever I wanted to
我可以采用你的公式
每当我想要的时候
and you couldn't
do a thing about it.
而你不能
做点什么吧。
Something about that woman
reminds me of my mother.
关于那个女人的一些事情
让我想起了我的母亲。
That's it.
就是这样。
Finally, victory  will  be mine.
最后，胜利将属于我。
I'll turn Eugene Krabs
into a powerless...
我会变成尤金克拉布斯
陷入无能为力的...
Baby.
婴儿。
Ooh, a penny.
哦，一分钱。
A trail of pennies.
一便士的踪迹。
Ooh...
哦...
I've done it.
我已经做到了。
Nothing can stop me now.
现在没有什么可以阻止我。
My goo goo gas
will transform Krabs
我的咕咕气体
将改变蟹蟹
into a tiny, helpless infant.
变成一个小而无助的婴儿。
The key to the Krusty Krab.
蟹堡王的钥匙。
This was easier than I hoped.
这比我希望的要容易。
Hmm.
唔。
He's a little bigger
than I imagined.
他稍微大一点
比我想象的要好。
Shiny...
闪亮的...
Plankton: Whoa!
浮游生物：哇！
No, no!
不，不！
Ah, ah, ahh!
啊啊啊啊！
Oof!
钱币！
Whoa!
哇！
Hey, a baby.
嘿，一个婴儿。
What are you doing out
here all alone, baby?
你在外面做什么
宝贝，独自一人在这里吗？
I'll take charge of you
until your mommy shows up.
我来负责你
直到你妈妈出现。
Oh, aren't you just too cute.
哦，你是不是太可爱了。
Coochie-coochie-coo.
咕咕咕。
Plankton: Hello...
浮游生物：你好……
If you're done making
a total fool out of yourself
如果你完成了制作
你自己简直就是个傻瓜
I could use some help
with this lock.
我需要一些帮助
有了这把锁。
Oh, sure thing, Plankton.
哦，当然可以，浮游生物。
There you go little guy.
给你，小家伙。
Yes.
是的。
My plan is working perfectly.
我的计划正在完美地进行。
Now that I've turned Krabs
into a helpless baby
现在我已经变成螃蟹了
变成一个无助的婴儿
the Krabby Patty formula
will be mine.
蟹黄饼配方
将是我的。
Eh?
呃？
Hello.
你好。
Police, police!
警察，警察！
Plankton: Fools...
浮游生物：笨蛋……
You'll never hold me.
你永远不会抱紧我。
These primitive shackles
are no match for my genius.
这些原始的枷锁
都敌不过我的天才。
That was easy.
那很容易。
Plankton: I'm free.
浮游生物：我自由了。
Free...
自由的...
Oh, Squidward.
哦，章鱼哥。
Thank Neptune, you're here.
感谢海王星，你来了。
I found this baby all alone.
我独自一人发现了这个婴儿。
But he wasn't really alone,
he was with Plankton
但他其实并不孤单，
他和浮游生物在一起
and he's not a baby.
而且他不是婴儿。
It's Mr. Krabs.
是蟹老板。
Plankton turned him
into an infant so he could
steal the Krabby Patty formula.
浮游生物把他变成了
进入婴儿，这样他就可以
偷走蟹黄派的配方。
What do we do, Squidward?
我们该怎么办，章鱼哥？
Don't know about you,
but I'm going
on my coffee break.
不知道你的情况，
但我要去
在我喝咖啡的休息时间。
A very long coffee break.
一个很长的咖啡休息时间。
And then that blasted
sponge called the cops.
然后就炸了
海绵报了警。
That's just not cricket.
那不是板球。
Now I'll never be
a tyrannical overlord.
现在我永远不会
一个残暴的霸主。
Karen: Do I have to tell you
how to do everything?
凯伦：我必须告诉你吗
怎样做一切？
Next time spray SpongeBob, too.
下次也喷海绵宝宝吧。
Not sure
I follow you.
不确定
我跟着你。
Listen carefully.
仔细听。
Spray...
喷...
Yes.
是的。
Sponge...
海绵...
Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。
Bob...
鲍勃...
Right.
正确的。
Too.
也。
Now you're just
talking Gibberish.
现在你只是
胡言乱语。
What I really need is to
我真正需要的是
spray Mr. Krabs and SpongeBob.
喷洒蟹蟹先生和海绵宝宝。
Ahh, that's just what...
啊啊，原来是这样啊……
I don't wanna hear anymore
我不想再听了
of your loony schemes, Karen.
你的疯狂计划，凯伦。
I've got work to do.
我还有工作要做。
Aw, what's wrong
Mr. Baby Krabs?
噢，怎么了
蟹宝宝先生？
Are you thirsty?
你渴吗？
That's it, drink up.
就这样，喝了。
OK, maybe you're hungry.
好吧，也许你饿了。
How about a nice
hot Krabby Patty?
怎么样一个好的
辣蟹饼？
Yikes, not even
a Krabby Patty helps.
哎呀，甚至没有
蟹肉饼有帮助。
How 'bout a stack of $20s?
一堆20美元怎么样？
"Hee..."
“嘿嘿……”
Plankton: Hands in the air.
浮游生物：双手举在空中。
: Plankton.
：浮游生物。
That's right, SpongeBob,
I'm back.
没错，海绵宝宝，
我回来了。
And you won't stop me this time.
这次你不会再阻止我了。
What?
什么？
SpongeBob's a baby
but Krabs is back to normal?
海绵宝宝还是个婴儿
但蟹老板恢复正常了吗？
It seems a second dose
acts as an antidote.
看来是第二剂了
作为解毒剂。
One squirt equals baby.
喷一喷就等于生宝宝。
Two squirts equals adult.
喷两次就等于成人。
Or is it three squirts for baby
还是给宝宝喷三喷
and four squirts for adults?
成人可以喷四次吗？
Barnacles,
I've run out of gas.
藤壶，
我的汽油用完了。
Ahem...
咳咳……
Krabs!
螃蟹们！
Nice diaper.
漂亮的尿布。
Plankton: Hold on, hold on,
I think I...
浮游生物：坚持住，坚持住，
我想我...
Yes, I've got it.
是的，我明白了。
There'd better be something
other than bills in here.
最好有一些东西
除了这里的账单。
Plankton.
浮游生物。
Peek-a-boo.
躲猫猫。
Ahh!
啊！
I can't tolerate
我无法忍受
your stinky gas.
你的臭气。
That makes two of us.
这就是我们两个人。
I don't do it
on purpose.
我不做
故意的。
You'll never
catch me, Plankton.
你永远不会
抓住我，浮游生物。
Never.
绝不。
Ooh, another penny.
哦，又一分钱。
Come to papa.
来找爸爸吧。
Now what were we doing?
现在我们在做什么？
This.
这。
What's the matter, baby?
怎么了，宝贝？
You gonna cry?
你会哭吗？
What the heck
happened to you?
到底是什么
你发生了什么事吗？
This isn't baby gas.
这不是婴儿气体。
It's senior citizen spray.
这是老年人喷雾。
Eh, what was that, sonny?
呃，那是什么，儿子？
Out of my way, methuselah.
别挡我的路，玛撒拉。
You're old and useless.
你老了，没用了。
Hold it right there.
把它握在那里。
Old people are our greatest
natural resource.
老人是我们最伟大的人
自然资源。
I salute you, elder citizenry.
我向你们致敬，年长的公民。
I'm getting old
listening to this.
我变老了
听这个。
Let's try this again.
让我们再试一次。
I remember when a quarter
used to cost a nickel.
我记得四分之一的时候
用于花费五分钱。
This baby gas is worthless...
这婴儿气体毫无价值……
At least you're way too old
至少你已经太老了
to stop me from stealing
a Krabby Patty.
阻止我偷窃
蟹肉饼。
What was that, sonny?
那是什么，儿子？
It'll take more time to explain
than you have left.
需要更多时间来解释
比你离开的时间还要长。
What?
什么？
He's got the Krabby Patty.
他有蟹黄饼。
Catch him.
抓住他。
Catch who?
抓住谁？
Oh,  gezhundheit.
哦，gezhundheit。
Victory is mine.
胜利是我的。
Ah!
啊!
Come back here,
you little whippersnapper.
回到这里，
你这个小自命不凡的人。
You kids get
off my lawn.
你们孩子们得到
离开我的草坪。
Whew.
呼。
Ooh, boy.
哦，男孩。
I'll catch up with you, boy.
我会追上你的，孩子。
I'm catching up
with my knitting.
我正在追赶
用我的编织。
That's it.
就是这样。
Knit, you little nitwit.
编织，你这个小白痴。
That was almost too easy.
这太容易了。
What? No!
什么？不！
I demand you
geezers release me!
我要求你
老兄放开我！
Right after the party...
聚会结束后...
The piñata party.
皮纳塔派对。
Plankton: What?
浮游生物：什么？
Man: That's for
calling us old.
男：那是为了
叫我们老了。
Hey, quit it.
嘿，别说了。
I want candy.
我想要糖果。
Plankton: No!
浮游生物：不！
One squirt, plus adult...
Carry the two
一喷，加上成人...
带着两个
gas vector minus
body weight, um-hm...
气体矢量减
体重，嗯……
Square root of SpongeBob...
海绵宝宝的平方根...
Of course.
当然。
The final ingredient
that I've been lacking.
最终成分
我一直缺乏的。
It's so simple, yet so evil.
就是这么简单，却又这么邪恶。
And I know
just the place to get it.
我知道
只是获得它的地方。
Excuse me.
打扰一下。
What aisle did you
get that from?
你走哪条路
从哪里得到的？
You mean the kelpo?
你是说凯尔波吗？
No, that thing.
不，那个东西。
The ugly, drippy, smelly thing.
丑陋的、滴水的、有臭味的东西。
Are you talking about my baby?
你在说我的宝宝吗？
Creep.
蠕变。
Ow, ow, ow!
噢，噢，噢！
Baby powder.
婴儿爽身粉。
This could be just what I need.
这可能正是我所需要的。
Hey, buddy.
嘿，伙计。
Is this made from real
or artificial babies?
这是真人制作的吗
还是人造婴儿？
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
噢，噢，噢，噢！
Plankton: That "powdered baby"
did the trick.
浮游生物：那个“粉宝宝”
成功了。
Now my baby gas
can't possibly fail.
现在我的宝贝气体
不可能失败。
Karen: Just like
all your other plans
凯伦：就像
你所有的其他计划
that couldn't possibly fail?
那不可能失败吗？
What is it now, Karen?
现在怎么样了，凯伦？
I'm saying you should
test your gas
我是说你应该
测试你的气体
before you run over there
all willy-nilly.
在你跑过去之前
都随心所欲。
That's an excellent idea.
这是个好主意。
And I know just the Guinea pig.
我只认识豚鼠。
: Plankton...
Don't you dare.
: 浮游生物...
你不敢。
Karen, speak to me.
凯伦，跟我说话。
It worked.
它起作用了。
Everyone say your "A-B-C's".
每个人都说出你的“A-B-C”。
Now when you
turn into babies...
现在当你
变成婴儿...
You stay babies.
你还是婴儿吧。
Hey, Krabs... Catch.
嘿，蟹蟹...抓住。
What's wrong,
little fellow?
怎么了，
小家伙？
Ahh!
啊！
My moment of triumph.
我的胜利时刻。
Whoa!
哇！
What the...
什么...
Oh, gross.
哦，太恶心了。
I command you to stop
drooling on me.
我命令你停下来
流口水在我身上。
Krabs: Goo.
蟹蟹：咕咕。
Put me down.
把我放下来。
Ow!
噢！
Stop it.
停止吧。
I'm an adult  .
我是一个成年人了。
Yeow!
哟！
Huh?
啊？
I don't believe it.
我不相信。
The Krabby Patty formula.
蟹黄饼配方。
He's teething on it.
他正在磨牙。
Give it here
给这里
you big stupid baby.
你这个大傻宝贝。
Ow.
噢。
I've got it.
我明白了。
Just like taking candy
from a baby.
就像吃糖果一样
来自一个婴儿。
Get it, Krabs?
明白了吗，蟹蟹？
Like taking candy from you.
就像从你手里夺走糖果一样。
Hey, what are you doing?
嘿，你在做什么？
Whoo...
呼...
Uh-oh.
呃哦。
Ahem.
咳咳。
Mama's evil little genius
needs a diaper!
妈妈的邪恶小天才
需要尿布！
Order up.
订购吧。
Go now and bless the taste buds
of your lucky connoisseur.
现在就去祝福味蕾
您幸运的鉴赏家。
Mwah.
哇。
It went in my mouth.
它进入了我的嘴。
Choking on sentiment.
情绪哽咽。
Like poison.
就像毒药一样。
OK, you sit this
one out Squidward.
好的，你坐这个
一出章鱼哥。
This will be a special delivery
from the chef.
这将是一次特殊递送
来自厨师。
For your dining pleasure.
为了您的用餐愉快。
Two double Krabby Patties
cooked to perfection
两块双层蟹肉饼
煮至完美
complimented by a side of coral
bits and a jumbo diet soda.
配以珊瑚的一面
碎块和一大杯无糖汽水。
Topped off with
a little extra love.
结束于
一点额外的爱。
Enjoy!
享受！
It's the little details
就是这些小细节
that they really appreciate,
isn't it, Squidward?
他们真的很感激，
不是吗，章鱼哥？
Uh...
呃...
Oh, yeah, you've really
touched  his  life.
哦，是的，你确实
触动了他的生活。
Nothing beats making quality
food for good people
没有什么比制造品质更好的了
为好人提供食物
with discriminating tastes.
具有辨别的品味。
Quality food?
优质食品？
Yeah!
是的！
Good people?
好人？
Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。
Discriminating tastes?
品味歧视？
Testify!
作证！
D'oh...
哦...
Only pathetic losers
with horrible taste
只有可悲的失败者
味道很糟糕
would eat this garbage.
会吃这些垃圾。
Squidward...
章鱼哥...
The Krusty clientele
needs to be cuddled
库斯蒂客户群
需要拥抱
and treated with respect.
并受到尊重。
There, there.
那里，那里。
Mr. Krabs would be ashamed.
蟹老板会感到羞愧的。
All right,
you filthy bilge rats.
好吧，
你们这些肮脏的舱底老鼠。
Mr. Krabs?
蟹老板？
Ya got three seconds
to get out of me restaurant
你有三秒时间
滚出我的餐厅
before I kick ya out.
在我把你踢出去之前
Fine, have it yer way.
好吧，随你便吧。
What's happening, Mr. Krabs?
发生了什么事，蟹老板？
Ah, we don't need
those losers anymore.
啊，我们不需要
那些失败者了。
I'm turning the restaurant
into one of those
fancy frou-frou places
我要转餐厅
进入其中之一
花哨的地方
where they charge big bucks
for itsy-bitsy portions.
他们收取大笔费用的地方
对于它的小部分。
Fancy...
想要...
frou-frou?
夫劳夫？
We're getting a gourmet chef
from the chef exchange program
我们请来了一位美食厨师
来自厨师交流计划
and I'm gonna raise
me prices to the roof.
我会提出
我的价格到了屋顶。
Chef exchange program?
厨师交流计划？
Oh, uh, yeah.
哦，呃，是的。
You're being shipped off
to some other restaurant
你正在被运走
去其他一些餐馆
somewhere far away from here.
离这里很远的地方。
The details are kind of hazy.
细节有点模糊。
But I packed your bags and
your bus leaves in five minutes.
但我收拾好你的行李
你的公共汽车五分钟后出发。
Heh, looks like it's early.
呵呵，看来还早呢。
it was that easy?
有那么容易吗？
: All these years?
: 这些年了？
I've underestimated the power
of public transportation.
我低估了力量
的公共交通。
Welcome to the Krusty Krab.
欢迎来到蟹堡王。
Does your middle name
happen to be
你的中间名吗
碰巧是
"No SpongeBob within a thousand
kilometers of here?"
“一千以内没有海绵宝宝
这里还有几公里？”
I find you disgusting.
我觉得你很恶心。
However, my culture dictates
that I must kiss you regardless.
然而，我的文化决定了
无论如何我都必须吻你。
Mwah, mwah...  .
哇哇哇……
Well, he's just as
affectionate as the boy.
嗯，他就像
像男孩一样深情。
But the surly attitude is
a step in the right direction.
但态度却是粗暴
朝着正确方向迈出的一步。
French Chef: What is
this rubbish?
法国厨师：什么是
这垃圾？
I would not wipe
my own bottom with this.
我不会擦
我对此有自己的底。
Start over.
重新开始。
And this...
还有这个...
I would not wash
my own bottom with this
我不会洗
我自己的底线
after carefully wiping
and wiping and wiping.
仔细擦拭后
以及擦拭和擦拭。
Now go stand in the corner
现在去站在角落里
and think about
what you have done.
并思考
你做了什么。
And where is my exchange chef?
我的交换厨师在哪里？
SpongeBob: Um,
right here, sir.
海绵宝宝：嗯，
就在这里，先生。
Oh, ho-ho-ho,
there you are.
哦，嗬嗬嗬，
你来了。
Bonjour.
你好。
Ooh...  .
哦....
Now...
现在...
Get to your station and
prepare me your best dish!
到达您的车站并
给我准备你最好吃的菜！
: Mwah.
: 哇。
Zis is not funny.
齐斯并不好笑。
And I certainly did not
exchange my top sous-chef
我当然没有
交换我的顶级副主厨
for a... How you say?
对于... 你怎么说？
Comedian!
喜剧演员！
Prepare me a gourmet dish...
给我准备一道美味佳肴...
Now!
现在！
I'm sure with all my years
in the kitchen
我确信用我所有的岁月
在厨房里
I can make something
other than...
我可以做点什么
除了...
Just warming up.
刚刚热身。
Ah!
啊!
Come on, SpongeBob.
来吧，海绵宝宝。
Ahh!
啊！
Just one egg and...
只需一个鸡蛋和...
No...  .
不...  。
Nope, that's not
it, either.
不，那不是
它，要么。
You are making
a mockery of my...
你正在做
对我的...的嘲讽
This taste is...
Is fantastic.
这个味道是...
太棒了。
What do you call it?
你怎么称呼它？
A Krabby Patty.
蟹肉饼。
Ze whole world must taste this.
全世界都必须尝尝这个。
French Man: Meanwhile,
at the Krusty Krab...
法国人：同时，
在蟹堡王...
Hey, Squidward.
嘿，章鱼哥。
Look at this.
看看这个。
We're charging $52 smackaroos
for this little guy
我们收费 52 美元
为了这个小家伙
Ohh... What is that?
哦...那是什么？
Heh, I don't know.
呵呵，我不知道。
Some kind of bean paste
or something.
某种豆沙
或者什么的。
Wrong,  monsieur.
错了，先生。
It is the rare fruit
of the kazook tree.
这是稀有水果
卡祖克树的。
So... It's supposed to smell
like rotten gym socks?
所以...应该闻起来
比如腐烂的运动袜？
Its naturally rancid odor
其自然腐臭气味
can only be neutralized
by shredded gold.
只能被中和
通过碎金。
Shredded  ... Gold?
撕碎...黄金？
Couldn't we use less
expensive ingredients?
我们不能少用一点吗
昂贵的成分？
Price can be no object
价格不是问题
when dealing with exquisite
food like zis.
在处理精致的事情时
像zis这样的食物。
It must be prepared with only
the finest ingredients
它必须只准备
最优质的原料
and eaten with only
the finest silverware
并只与
最好的银器
while sitting
on the finest furniture.
坐着时
在最好的家具上。
Zis is not the chair I ordered.
Zis 不是我订购的椅子。
Yeah, well, you see,
those were out of stock.
是的，好吧，你看，
那些已经缺货了。
And zis fork of plastic...
还有塑料叉子...
Spray painted to look silver,
is it not?
喷漆成银色，
不是吗？
I cannot prepare food
我无法准备食物
under these conditions!
在这样的条件下！
Monsieur  SpongeBob.
海绵宝宝先生。
Although it is
in direct violation
虽然它是
直接违反
of the chef
exchange program rules
厨师的
交换项目规则
let me assure you
that these kisses
让我向你保证
这些吻
are not merely a formality.
不仅仅是一种形式。
They are genuine.
他们是真诚的。
I am sure that this is only
the beginning of a long and...
我确信这只是
漫长而……的开始
Well, my time here is up.
好吧，我在这里的时间到了。
I'm officially a Krusty Krab
employee once again.
我正式成为蟹堡王了
再次是员工。
I apologize,  monsieur  SpongeBob
我很抱歉，海绵宝宝先生
but you see,
my customers have grown
但你看，
我的客户已经成长
rather fond
of your Krabby Patties.
相当喜欢
你的蟹黄饼。
The Krabby Patties.
蟹肉饼。
I almost forgot.
我差点忘了。
These babies also belong
to the Krusty Krab.
这些宝贝也属于
到蟹堡王。
What?
什么？
So long.
这么久。
Wait, just one more.
等等，还有一个。
I'm sorry...
对不起...
But I've got to go...
但我得走了...
I'm ruined  .
我毁了。
Busted  .
被抓了。
Hello?
你好？
Pearl:  : Daddy,
the house is full of burglars.
珍珠：：爸爸，
房子里挤满了窃贼。
Oh-ho, no, those aren't
burglars, Pearl.
噢，不，那些不是
窃贼，珍珠。
Those are just
friendly repo men.
这些只是
友好的回购人。
Mr. Krabs, tell these guys
to let go of me.
蟹老板，告诉这些家伙
放开我。
Uh, well, you know, until
I come up with the money I owe
呃，好吧，你知道，直到
我拿出我欠的钱
I'm afraid you'll be stayin'
with these nice gents.
我担心你会留下来
和这些好先生们。
You sold me?
你把我卖了？
No...
不...
Bartered, is more like it.
物物交换，更像是这样。
They keep you-
I keep my kneecaps, heh-heh.
他们让你——
我保留膝盖了，呵呵。
Come on, Mac.
来吧，麦克。
You're pathetic.
你真可怜。
Oh, Mr. Le Schnook.
哦，勒施努克先生。
I've lost everything.
我已经失去了一切。
I'm bankrupt.
我破产了。
You and your fancy eats
are all I got left now.
你和你的美食
我现在只剩下这些了。
Not quite.
不完全是。
My time in the chef's exchange
program has expired
我在厨师交流的时光
计划已过期
so my "eats" and I are leaving.
所以我的“吃”然后我就要离开了。
This is for you.
这是给您的。
Is it money?
是钱吗？
It is the bill
for my services.
这是账单
为了我的服务。
One side, please.
请一侧。
Oh, I've been such a fool.
哦，我真是个傻瓜。
I turned away SpongeBob
我拒绝了海绵宝宝
the best fry cook I ever had
我吃过的最好的炒菜厨师
and it cost me everything.
这让我付出了一切。
SpongeBob: Mr. Krabs.
海绵宝宝：蟹老板。
Oh, I can still hear
his sweet little voice.
哦，我还能听到
他甜美的小声音。
: Mr. Krabs.
: 蟹老板。
OK, now I'm scared.
好吧，现在我很害怕。
Mr. Krabs!
蟹老板！
Darn his cursed,
mocking voice, I...
该死的他的诅咒，
嘲讽的声音，我……
SpongeBob?
海绵宝宝？
Ahoy, Mr. Krabs.
嘿，蟹老板。
SpongeBob, me boy,
you've come back.
海绵宝宝，我的男孩，
你回来了。
And you've brought customers.
你带来了客户。
Well, Mr. Squidward,
all's well that ends well.
那么，章鱼哥先生，
一切都好，结局好。
I got me poor disgustin'
old clientele back
我让我很恶心
老顾客回归
and me rich disgustin'
new clientele to boot.
和我有钱恶心
新客户的启动。
I'm back in business.
我又回来做生意了
Couldn't you at least
give them tables to eat on?
你至少不能
给他们桌子吃饭吗？
Oh-ho... No way.
噢噢……不可能。
See, I've learned ya can't
buy me customer loyalty
看，我知道你不能
给我买客户忠诚度
with fancy tables,
frou-frou food, or even
sanitary conditions.
配上精美的桌子，
frou-frou食物，甚至
卫生条件。
Hey, get back you,
eat your own...
嘿，回来吧，
吃自己的...
Nope, just good food
prepared with love.
不，只是好吃
用爱来准备。
Isn't that right, SpongeBob?
不是吗，海绵宝宝？
You got it, Mr. Krabs.
你明白了，蟹老板。
Mwah.
哇。